export const AllQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Relative minor of C",
    answer: ['a']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of A",
    answer: ['f#', 'fs']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of B",
    answer: ['gs', 'g#']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of D",
    answer: ['b']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of E",
    answer: ['c#', 'cs']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of F",
    answer: ['d']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of G",
    answer: ['e']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of B♭",
    answer: ['g']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of E♭",
    answer: ['c']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of A♭",
    answer: ['f']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of D♭",
    answer: ['bf', 'b♭']
  },
  {
    question: "Relative minor of F#",
    answer: ['ds', 'd#']
  },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of C",
  //   answer: ['ef', 'e♭']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of G",
  //   answer: ['bf', 'b♭']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of F",
  //   answer: ['af', 'a♭']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of E",
  //   answer: ['g']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of A",
  //   answer: ['c']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of D",
  //   answer: ['f']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of F#",
  //   answer: ['a']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of B♭",
  //   answer: ['df', 'd♭']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of E♭/d#",
  //   answer: ['gf', 'g♭', 'fs', 'f#']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of g#",
  //   answer: ['b']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of c#",
  //   answer: ['e']
  // },
  // {

  //   question: "Relative major of B",
  //   answer: ['d']
  // }
  {
    question: "V of C",
    answer: ['g']
  },
  {
    question: "V of A",
    answer: ['e']
  },
  {
    question: "V of B",
    answer: ['fs', 'f#']
  },
  {
    question: "V of D",
    answer: ['a']
  },
  {
    question: "V of E",
    answer: ['b']
  },
  {
    question: "V of F",
    answer: ['c']
  },
  {
    question: "V of G",
    answer: ['d']
  },
  {
    question: "V of B♭",
    answer: ['f']
  },
  {
    question: "V of E♭",
    answer: ['bf', 'b♭']
  },
  {
    question: "V of A♭",
    answer: ['ef', 'e♭']
  },
  {
    question: "V of D♭",
    answer: ['af', 'a♭']
  },
  {
    question: "V of F#",
    answer: ['cs', 'c#']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of C",
    answer: ['f']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of A",
    answer: ['d']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of B",
    answer: ['e']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of D",
    answer: ['g']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of E",
    answer: ['a']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of F",
    answer: ['b♭', 'bf']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of G",
    answer: ['c']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of B♭",
    answer: ['e♭', 'ef']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of E♭",
    answer: ['a♭', 'af']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of A♭",
    answer: ['d♭', 'df']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of D♭",
    answer: ['g♭', 'gf']
  },
  {
    question: "IV of F#",
    answer: ['b']
  }
];